Boss, the guy's
a total loser.
Okay?
Every play he ran,
he got from me.
The only reason he won last game is because I,
I gave him the
plan in advance.
So that's how
he pulled it off?
Damn, acting like all our plays were his ideas?
Fuck!
Exactly.
That's why I fired him.
Well, if he's that useless,
good riddance!
But you listen
to me, West.
If you lose to a bunch of pussies like that again,
I will fucking destroy you.
You understand me?
Yes, sir.
Don't
fuck with me.
Yes, sir.
Damn it!
The only reason
we ever won
was because we followed Ted's game plan.
I never should
have fired him
in the heat of
the moment.
This...
This is Ted's playbook.
We're saved.
Hey, hey.
Why aren't you running the plays I called?
Look, it's
three to fifteen
at half, okay?
You scored three points.
You're a
washed-up assistant,
dumped by his wife.
What gives you the right to even coach us?
Hey, you need to watch-
Scott,
if you want to
win this game,
you will run my plays.
Period.
Your plays are trash!
Okay then.
You're benched.
Next man up!
Wait, what?
Seriously?
You're benching me?
Look,
you may be the best player on our team,
but I don't need a player who can't follow orders.
You are done here.
Your plays are horseshit!
Okay, no one can make
a perfect forty-yard
throw like that.
It's impossible!
You're not fit to be
the head coach!
Or an assistant coach!
Was that hard?
Holy shit!